<resources>
    <!--
      Copyright 2020 The Android Open Source Project
      Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except
      in compliance with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
      Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the License
      is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express
      or implied. See the License for the specific language governing permissions and limitations under
      the License.
      -->
    <string name="app_name">AndroidDevChallenge</string>
    <string-array name="breed">
        <item>Affenpinscher</item>
        <item>Beagle</item>
        <item>Boxer</item>
        <item>Bullador</item>
        <item>Bulldog</item>
        <item>Cavapoo</item>
        <item>Dachshund</item>
        <item>Dalmatian</item>
        <item>Doberman Pinscher</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="desc">
        <item>The Affenpinscher, also known as the \"Monkey Dog\" (\"affen\" means \"ape/monkey\" in German, and \"pinscher\"
            means \"terrier\"), is small but feisty, full of spunk and energy.
            This mustachioed little devil is descended from the numerous small
            terriers that populated 17th and 18th century stables and shops
            throughout Europe, ridding them of rats and mice.</item>

        <item>Small, compact, and hardy, Beagles are active companions for kids and adults alike.
            Canines of this dog breed are merry and fun loving, but being hounds,
            they can also be stubborn and require patient, creative training techniques.
            Their noses guide them through life, and they\’re never happier than when following an interesting scent.
            Beagles originally were bred as scenthounds to track small game, mostly rabbits and hare.
            They\’re still used for this purpose in many countries today,
            including the United States. But you\’ll find plenty of these pups
            living as companion dogs and loving, furry family members.</item>
        <item>Boxer dogs were originally bred to be medium-size guard dogs.
            Today, although they are a part of the AKC\’s Working Group,
            Boxers mostly find homes as loving family companions. That said,
            they still retain their high energy levels and need plenty of exercise.
            Square-jawed and muscular, this breed is the George
            Clooney of the dog world–a looker with a sense of humor
            and an underlying sweetness. They adore their families and will
            also appreciate consistent training that doesn\’t rely on harsh reprimands.</item>
        <item>
            The Bullador is a mixed breed dog–a cross between the Labrador and
            English Bulldog breeds. These pups fall into the medium-to-large size range.
            Active and loyal, Bulladors inherited some of the best traits from both of their parents.
            Bulladors should not be confused with Labrabulls–Labrador
            Retriever and Pit Bull mixes. Despite their unfortunate status as a
            designer breed, you can find these mixed pups in shelters and breed
            specific rescues, so remember to adopt!
        </item>
        <item>The Bulldog was originally used to drive cattle to market and to compete in a bloody sport called bullbaiting.
            Today, they\’re gentle companions who love kids.
            Even though these are purebred dogs, you may find them in the care of shelters or
            rescue groups. Remember to adopt!</item>
        <item>The Cavapoo is a mixed breed dog — a cross between the Cavalier King Charles Spaniel and Poodle dog breeds.
            Outgoing, playful, and curious, these pups inherit some of the best traits from both of their parents.
            Cavapoos go by several names, including Cavadoodle and Cavoodle.
            Despite their unfortunate status as a designer breed, you can find these
            mixed breed dogs in shelters and rescues, so remember to adopt!</item>
        <item>Dachshunds are scent hound dogs bred to hunt badgers and other tunneling animals, rabbits, and foxes.
            Hunters even used packs of Dachshunds to trail wild boar.
            Today their versatility makes them excellent family companions, show dogs, and small-game hunters.

But don\’t let this pup fool you. Dogs of this breed might be,
            as legendary literary critic and humorous journalist
            H. L. Mencken said, \“half a dog high and a dog and a half long,\”
            but this small, drop-eared dog is tough enough to take on a badger.
            In fact, that\’s how they got their name (Dachs meaning badger; hund meaning dog).

</item>
        <item>Best known as the star of Disney\’s 101 Dalmatians,
            this sleek and athletic Dalmatian dog breed has a history
            that goes back several hundred years. They started out as a
            coach dog but also served in many other capacities, including hunter, firehouse dog, and circus performer.
            Even though these are purebred dogs,
            you may find them in the care of shelters
            or rescue groups. Remember to adopt! Don\’t shop if you want to bring a dog home.</item>
        <item>Doberman Pinschers originated in Germany during the late 19th century,
            mostly bred as guard dogs. Their exact ancestry is unknown,
            but they\’re believed to be a mixture of many dog breeds, including
            the Rottweiler, Black and Tan Terrier, and German Pinscher.
            With their sleek coat, athletic build, and regal appearance,
            this pup looks like an aristocrat. They\’re highly energetic
            and smart dogs who perform well in police and military work,
            canine sports, and as family guardians and companions.</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>